Good morning!
I'll do my best!
I'm a little less porous this morning.
Yay!
Oh, did you say with water? Something like...
Bye bye!
Look what they brought us!
The Yajima family sent us some muscats, and now we're out of one.
We've already run out of one. No problem.
I'll take a Kyushu I.M. from the Kyushu family.
Thank you very much.
This is the best kimono I've ever seen.
It's the best kimono I've ever seen.
Here's the package.
New email.
It's a heart, send it back.
It's a heart.
Later.
And...
The day before yesterday.
Good morning!
One-man live concert
First day!
I woke up early in the morning and came here.
We'll be rehearsing later.
That's right.
We've gone through a lot of hardships over the years to get here.
We had some fights.
Especially...
Yuna and Miyu...
They fought every time they met.
Fist fights.
It happened every day.
It was really tough.
Laughs.
It was hard.
There were times when it was hard.
To be honest.
There were times when there was nothing I could do.
But in those times, it was all because of that
AM.
AM and ICH...
They kind of calmed us down and said, “It's going to be okay.
They were there for us, telling us it was going to be all right.
I think that's why we are here today.
Who can understand?
Good morning.
Here's today's hair and makeup.
I thought...
But the bangs will probably get in the way.
After rehearsal.
I think it will look like this after rehearsal.
This is how I want to go to rehearsal
One-man show
I hope everyone enjoys the show!
Thank you very much.
Here we go!
something
Last time it was a one-man event.
I had a lot of fun with everyone.
The concept was a little bit like this.
I've been thinking about it a little bit.
It's been a year since I've had a one-man show.
I feel a little nostalgic.
I'll do my best.
We're in the group today, right?
We're in the group that's going to do the show, and the other two guys had their bangs down, so we're in the group that's going to do the show.
The first two guys were wearing their bangs down.
So we had no choice but to give it to them.
Hey, hey, hey.
Look up.
They were looking up.
Eye to eye.
I want you to stand in the second position of the chorus
The part of VG
2 rust half VG
What's this?
Tone number?
By the way...
Was it 3.5?
3.5, right?
I think it's 2.5.
7.5 in 2.5, 2.5, 3.5.
Make it 7.5 with one voice.
Maybe with another voice.
By the way.
This is just a little bit of pre-stuffing.
It's very important.
Yes, it is.
Just a little bit.
That's right.
When you're investing in a block, you have to be very careful with this.
Right, right.
Basically, before you ask.
I'm going to ask you...
Yuna Haruma is about the navel.
Yes, sir.
I'm pretty sure it's someone who says the word
Yes.
You mean like me?
Yes, and people who say things you don't like when they're served, like, for sure, yes, look, you mean like me? Yes.
And then we'll do it right the full time.
Ice Cream Encore
I want to see the tension in the encore.
So let's make sure we do that.
There's a lot of tension this time.
I say Shikoku, our hope for the future.
Even if the voice always comes from the bottom...
I don't even talk if it's screaming
We're on top of it, even if it's just the two of us
I say, even if it's just the two of us
Thank you for the rehearsal. Thank you very much for the rehearsal, and please do the same for the performance.
Thank you very much.
Don't mind me, friend.
It's the most beautiful just the way it is.
Oh...
We have 25 minutes until the show.
Everyone is hurrying to get dressed and do their hair and makeup. Aaaaahhh, 25 minutes until the show.
Everyone is rushing to change and do their hair and makeup.
Today is a two-part show, and we just did a block show, so it's actually already the third part.
We have to go to the end.
What are you going to do until the end? What about you, Haruma?
What? I'm going to push it to the end.
Yay!
But what I'm going to do is the same.
I'm just trying to get the rubbers and everyone else excited.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Whenever the scent comes, I'll do my best.
Yes, I'll make it come out.
Yes, thank you very much.
I'll take it as it is
Fallin' for you
Here it comes! One-man live show!
Yay!
There's one thing that Love One is determined to deliver
We want to make you want to come back again.
and to make you want to come back and listen to the music of Love One so that you can find a place in your heart.
Let's keep up the good work!
Let's continue to do our best from now on.
It's over!
Like a general manager.
We've got a minute or two left in the show.
Let's do our best!
We are One For One
For this day, we
We have prepared our pass as it is
I hope we can deliver it to you all!
I'm sorry to say this, but
I'll do my best!
I'll do my best, Kada-chan-san!
I'm off!
Let's try!
Seino
Ei-ei-ei-o! I'm going to challenge you!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's a hard line.
man, that line is so hard!
I'm looking forward to it!
I'll see you later.
Let's have fun.
Let's entertain them.
Let's entertain them. That's what we do best.
Love them.
Love you, love you, love you, love you, love you
Come on. Let's go.
We're doing our best!
Voice of the staff
Voices of Staff
Staff's VoiceStaff's VoiceStaff's VoiceThere is still more to come.
Because it will not come true even if it is imminent someday
Look, look, look, look, let your youth be engraved
comedy is a page of comedy
summer and scenes are staged
the story starts here
That's all, WE ARE ONE OF ONE HEART
it was ONE OF ONE HEART
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
So, that's the end of the first part.
Well, it's the first time in a long time that we had two parts.
It's been a while since we've had two parts.
I don't know if we have enough time.
But in the meantime, it was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
It was great.
I gave it everything I had.
I'm starving.
All of it.
I got it all out.
It was fun.
Please take care of the second part, too.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
All right.
Some of it went by really fast.
It really did.
Yes, it went by really fast.
It went by really fast.
And now for the second part.
I'm 20 years old.
I can't do this.
It was a lot of fun.
Part 1
Sasaki's words at the end of the show were amazing.
There were some fans in tears when he said “All right”.
I was so moved...
I don't know how to say it... I was really moved.
I was also moved by the middle part of the show, under the blazing sun, Girls Forever, etc.
I enjoyed the parts I enjoyed.
And I was able to immerse myself in the worldview
I was able to do that.
I felt a strong bond with the fans.
I felt like I had a strong bond with the fans.
I felt like I became one with my fans.
I hope we can continue like this for the next two minutes.
I hope we can continue this way and deliver to you all
I hope I can show you how much Love Arm has grown.
I enjoyed the first part.
It was fun.
We have a lot more things to reflect on.
I hope we can make the most of them in Dream.
Thank you all so much for coming!
This is awesome!
You have to see this.
Please don't look at this!
This is Koekun's food!
Please stop!
No, it's not.
Yes, but...
I really like the way this looks.
The way it looks...
I love the way it looks.
I love apple pie.
Too stylish!
I did the same thing as you.
Really?
I'm glad I like you.
Wow!
This is cold!
I'll do the apres-consumption report.
Just eat in silence.
Okay.
Wow, I kind of like apple pie with flour on top.
So this is perfect for my mood!
So I'm going to take a bite.
I'm going to take a tiny bite here for the photo shoot!
Yes, ah, ah, is it good? Mogoo!
Mogoo, mogoo!
Oh!
This is the same apple pie I had in the fifth grade.
It's a little different, but it tastes almost exactly the same!
It's delicious.
What do you mean?
I was eating here by myself, and they all came over.
They love me so much. We are one of a heart.
Whoo!
Not bad, huh?
Love has its moments.
Oh, it was real.
During my performance.
I made a heart as L4U's love.
If you make a heart like this, your voice will be on my cheek.
It's going to ring.
What's this?
I did it!
What's wrong with your cheek?
I did it.
I said, “I love your cheeks.
I'm going that way because I like that way.
I did it!
I was so happy.
As a voice geek
Part of me was really happy, as a voice geek.
The first part was really...
Well, I was overwhelmed by the enthusiasm of everyone.
I was overwhelmed by the enthusiasm of the fans.
I had a few things that I regretted.
I had a lot of fun at the show.
I would like to enjoy the second part more by fixing the sea level exhibition.
I would like to enjoy the second part more, so I would like to fix some things to improve and enjoy the second part more.
I will do my best!
This is the end of the second part,
It's over.
Well, now that it's over, the hair and makeup have changed, hasn't it?
Yes, it did.
Some members have changed slightly, but some have changed drastically.
Yes, there are some.
They put lame on their hair, which is unusual.
Thank you very much.
Your eyes are flashy.
I'm going to do it in a flashy way.
Her hair is a heart, too. You're really into it. I'm really into it. Thank you for the rare opportunity to put lame and such on your eyes.
I'm going to do my hair in a heart shape.
Hearts....
You're really into it, aren't you?
I'm really into it.
You're really into it.
Thank you very much.
Do you have a spirit point?
What's the point of being enthusiastic?
Like the different color of the fingers in the earpiece.
It's the same.
You know, I usually don't wear my hair in a high polly tail.
I usually don't do that because my head gets tired.
But today I went all out.
I'm getting a storm of applause for Runo-chan, who put herself on the line to do the fony-tail for everyone, even though her head was tired,
I am surprisingly not tired.
I would be happy if you could take that one and tell me what you appreciate about the people who are watching you and what your vision is for the future.
Future prospects?
Yes, I would like to know what the future holds.
I am very grateful to all of you who came to see the show today,
I am also very grateful to those who support us from all over the world.
Because of you, we are able to stand on the stage with such a good feeling each and every time,
I am really full of feelings!
Please take a look at this.
I think the information has been released a little bit.
At Hulic Hall.
Hulic Hall.
I'll be doing a one-man show there.
Next time.
Thanks to all of you, we'll be back like this.
This is the first time you're announcing a one-man show at a one-man show.
What?
That's right.
What? Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Something is happening, and we'd like to continue working hard on the 2 minutes,
Please enjoy the making of the film as well.
Bye-bye! I'll do my best!
I think some parts of the film have been completed,
We only have a part left, so let's give it all we've got and move on to the next part!
Our hearts are one!
Yeah!
Burn for Hush!
Here comes the second part!
It's going to be tough!
We're full of them, so I'm going to do my best.
This is the second part.
I'll see you all at the one-man show
In six months.
It's more than half a year.
I'm going to do my best for the last time.
I'll do my best!
I can't stand it, I'm tearing up, I'm tearing up.
The pattern of blooming flowers
When I think of tomorrow
I feel as if I can't go on like this
I have an announcement.
What is it? It's not like some?
No, sir.
No, sir. No, it's not.
On July 19th and 20th next year.
July 19th and 20th next year at Curic Hall.
Thank you very much!
2DAYS!
Thank you very much.
It's your first time, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Two.
I'm so happy.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is the first time that Love Bang will be performing two days in a row.
I'm really happy, thank you very much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Recently, many of you have come to know of our existence through our song “Aise supremely scattered our days.
I think many of you came to the concert for the first time today.
Our second album, “Aise supremely scattered our day” is a song that we've been working on for the past 2024 years.
We have been walking in 2024, a year filled with new encounters
It has been a year full of new encounters
Looking back, I really feel that it was a year full of new encounters.
The year 2025 will be a year of walking forward with our third album “Shaking Spirit”.
One of the lead songs, “The Story Starts Here,” is a song that expresses our determination to make the most of the year.
It is a song that is filled to the fullest with our current determination.
It starts with an unchanging prologue
Towards the endless epilogue
I hope that we can leave our footprints steadily one by one
And believing that one day it will shine brightly
I'll start drawing the rest of the story tomorrow.
It's your real
One of One Heart
One of One Heart Thank you very much
It's your real One of One Heart One of One Heart
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you thank you thank you thank you
Thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I was seriously about to cry.
Thank you for your hard work. It's over. I was a little anxious today,
I couldn't say wow to the camera,
It's over for me.
I've been doing some strange things, things we've been doing on our own,
I just have to believe in what I've done, trust myself, and enjoy myself,
Enjoy all kinds of things,
I think I was able to enjoy many things, and I hope that the audience was able to come out,
I think we were able to get a good turnout from the audience, but there were also many challenges that I gained from today's performance,
But there were many challenges that we learned from today's performance, and we have already decided on our next one-man show in July,
I'm looking forward to that,
So, we are going to have a one-man show in July, so we are going to have a special show for that.
I'm going to have a special for the next one-man show in July,
Pingo's teacher, Pingo Reach, and Lipocher,
Let's make sure to fill up the fürik homer!
2DAYS!
I'll definitely fill it up.
I love the feeling of having done it all.
It's like I've been in a sauna and I'm ready to go.
Wow, this is a great plan!
I'll do my best to be a lucky charm like an eel!
One One Heart, I really want to continue to do my best so that I can show you all how much I've grown.
Thank you all very much for today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for the close-up camera, and thank you very much for the whole day of making of the show.
I'm going to miss you a little bit.
I'm a little sad to say goodbye to the making of this show.
I'm going to end today.
I'm going to give you a little closure.
I think I'll give it to you.
Here we go.
May I take your hand?
All right.
What is it?
The lights just came on at this time
bye-bye
From rehearsal to the show
thank you so much thank you so much
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you again in the future.